

Maverick Dean G. Santos Bachelor of Science in Information Technology

Contact

09480192203 maverickdeansantos951@gmail.com

Education

Senior High Graduate Louella Gotladera Alcoba National High School

2018-2020

College Graduate

Sorsogon State University (Bulan Campus)

2020-2024

Skills

- Have basic knowledge in Microsoft Offices.
- Have basic knowledge about computers.
- Have basic knowledge incoding.

References

Provided upon request.

Summary

Hi Ma'am/ Sir, My name is Maverick Dean G. Santos, Graduated at Sorsogon State University (Bulan 163 Gliponeo Street, Butag, Bulan, Sosogon Campus) with degree of Bachelor of Science in Information Technology, I don't have yet experiences in any work but I have experience in gathering some important documents and sorting it out just like what I do when I OJT at DepEd Sorsogon. I can also do a lot of works and I'm willing to learn a lot from your company.

Work Experience

OJT

Assisting at CID CHIEF OFFICE

2024 - Present

- · Assisting and scanning some documents OR code to be record.
- · Incoding some important Travel Order of employees.

SKC (Sports Kinetcs Club)

Officer

2023-2024

- · Providing needs of players of our schools like basketball and any sports.
- We are in charge of any events that connected to our organization such as Intramurals and SORSU Olympics.